Prehistoric Bimbos in Armageddon City is a science fiction,
comedy, fantasy film directed by Todd Sheets.
An evil overload and his cyborg army plot to control the world.
Trianna and her bimbo tribe set out to stop them.
Trianna, played by Tonia Monahan.
Gabrielle, played by Holly Starr.
Larry, played by Matthew Lewis.
Dillea, played by Jenny Admire.
Doc, played by Veronica Orr.
Kyree, played by Cheryl Metz.
This is a list of film director and film score composer collaborations (names
beginning with A–C) who have worked together on multiple projects.
For a complete list of collaborations, see the main article.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.